<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Mech game]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>Mech game</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 04:33:46 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 04:33:43 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Ammo Belt Pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This backpack has an ammo belt that can be fed to a belt weapon. It can hold up to three reloads of a belt fed weapon. This backpack can be reloaded with a use per supply box. It gets attached to a specific weapon.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Ammo Belt Pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Ammo Belt Pack.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Backpack rules]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Your mech can only carry one backpack at a time. Ammo backpacks allow other players to assist you with reloading. While other backpacks let you preform other actions or carry extra supplies. Mech backpacks cannot be wore or carried by out of mech characters.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Backpack rules.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Backpack rules.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:29:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Carry Pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This barrel/crate like backpack can hold a few boxes of supply and carry a person or other item. It can hold up to 3 <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Rules%2FSupply%20box" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Rules%2FSupply box" target="_blank">supply boxes</a> and an other item or person. While a person is being carried they can still use their weapons and shoot out at other creatures. While a person is in the carry pack they have heavy cover. The carry pack has 1 hit point.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Carry Pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Carry Pack.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 01:22:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Curl Pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This pack is designed to curl up mechs and fit them into smaller spaces. It works great for storage, rolling through tunnels, and shooting them out of deployment chutes. As an action you can activate your curl pack and gain the following benefits: +1 to armor rating, +10 movement speed, and you can fit in human sized spaces. You have the following restrictions: You can’t use equipment you aren’t carrying, you cannot shoot guns with a recoil higher than 3, and you have a -2 to any Str checks. You can use an action to stand up and end the curl. The pack has 2 hit points and when it drops to 0 you take the stand up action on your next turn.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Curl Pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Curl Pack.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:50:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Drone Pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These specialized harness holds a single 1m octocopter, that can carry almost any equipment. Once per round you can spend an action to manipulate the drone causing it to move and take another action. It has a 2 in all stats with a AR of 2 it has 2 hit points and cannot be damaged on your back. You can spend an action and a charge to repair it 2 hit points, Then it can redeployed. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Drone Pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Drone Pack.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 22:22:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grenade Pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This backpack holds ]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Grenade Pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Grenade Pack.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 04:58:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heavy Ammo Pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This modified version of the Ammo Pack is only useful for carrying heavy shells, such as those used by the RR10 and the Rocket Launcher. It can carry up to 8 shells, rockets or other single use ammunition. It has no hit points but you may expend two ammo to replace 1 damage.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Heavy Ammo Pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Heavy Ammo Pack.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 01:27:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jump pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This two canister backpack boosts mechs great distances. As part of a move action you can expend a charge to jump up to 60m and land without suffering any fall damage. You can This item has 2 hit point. If it has 1 of point the distance you can jump is halved.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Jump pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Jump pack.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:22:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Large Fuel Tank]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This extra massive canister is fed into one of you weapons that requires the fuel ammo type. This tank is designed to protect that fuel from the environment and stop it from exploding. This fuel tank can hold up to 3 reloads for a single weapon and 1 reload can be expended to generate 2 charges. While a weapon is hooked up to this they can not and do not need to be reloaded as an action, you can remove a charge from this item and reload them. As an action you can pour a fuel tank of that weapon to give this backpack a use pack.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Large Fuel Tank.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Large Fuel Tank.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:37:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Light Ammo pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This bag is perfect for carrying large shells or extra ammo. This pack can carry up to 8 clips of a specific ammo (If there are multiple types specify the amount of each.), and allows anyone to assist the reload of the carrier. It’s used with weapons that guzzle ammo. This pack cannot hold Heavy weapon ammo, single shells, or other large ammunition.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Light Ammo pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Light Ammo pack.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 08:41:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Massive capacitor pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This giant battery is carried on the outside of your mech. It’s wired in to your mech’s back and lets it run indefinitely. This massive capacitor holds 10 charges and it has 4 hit points. Charges from this capacitor can be moved into other capacitors. Anytime this pack takes damage it loses 2 charges. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Massive capacitor pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Massive capacitor pack.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 02:39:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Supply pack]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This giant bag has several pockets for extra equipment and spare supplies. It’s specially packed for each mission with whatever you’ll need before you need it. You or another creature can use an action to grab one of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Rules%2FSupply%20box" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Rules%2FSupply box" target="_blank">supply box</a> and pull out an item. This bag can carry up to 6 supply boxes. It has no hit points but 2 supply boxes can be destroyed for 1 damage.]]></description><link>Equipment/Backpacks/Supply pack.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Backpacks/Supply pack.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:12:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Armor plate]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This is the most basic way for your mech to stay alive when bullets are flying. This item is part of your standard starting equipment. It gives a +1 to Armor rating and has 1 hit point. It cannot be repaired. Unless you have special upgrades or equipment you cannot wear more than one of these at a time. They can replaced on your mech during a break. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Defense/Armor plate.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Defense/Armor plate.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:35:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flak Vest]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This vest fits over your pilot and gives them 1 additional HP and a +2 to AR when they're out of the mech. It has no hit points or uses.]]></description><link>Equipment/Defense/Flak Vest.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Defense/Flak Vest.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:41:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Force Projector]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This device emits an energy shield around you. While this shield is up any damage you would take is put into the shield instead. If you take 4 or more damage in a single hit the Force Projector takes 1 damage and breaks. The shield has 1 hit point (marked as a use) and you can use an action and a charge to reactivate the shield. The force projector has 1 hit point.]]></description><link>Equipment/Defense/Force Projector.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Defense/Force Projector.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:14:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heavy Armor Plate]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This extra heavy armor plate protects you from some projectiles and melee attacks. While you have this equipped you gain a +2 to armor rating. It has 3 hit points and can be repaired. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Defense/Heavy Armor Plate.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Defense/Heavy Armor Plate.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 23:26:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heavy Ballistic Shield]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This heavy shield is designed to protect mechs from incoming attacks. It fits on one arm and can be switched from arm to arm. After you move you can set a direction that the shield will protect you from. Also you can pick an ally adjacent to you that’s not on the same side of you as the shield is facing. The shield has 3 hit points but you cannot assign damage to it. It has its own stats and doesn’t roll to avoid damage.<br>
Str 13 Agl 10 Com 8 Sen 10 Def 11]]></description><link>Equipment/Defense/Heavy Ballistic Shield.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Defense/Heavy Ballistic Shield.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 15:50:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Repair Vials]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Small capsules filled with repairing nano bots to patch holes in various bit of equipment. They shatter on impact when thrown or whacked on a device.<br>
Set size: 2<br>
Throw Range: Str Score x 10m<br>
Effect: The restore 1 hit point to any equipment, upgrade or part (Non pilot).]]></description><link>Equipment/Defense/Repair Vials.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Defense/Repair Vials.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 18:28:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Claymore Mine]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Claymore mines are perfect for setting traps and blasting enemies away. Just set one up and wait for an enemy to approach. Make sure you have it facing the right way or you might get turned into Jelly. You can spend an action to plant one claymore on a space (specifying the direction it’s facing) When a creature moves into the claymore’s space or the space the claymore is facing it detonates.<br>
Dealing 2 damage to the creature that triggers it and 1 damage in a 3 space cone in the way the claymore is facing. You can carry 2 claymores per equipment slot.]]></description><link>Equipment/Fortifcations/Claymore Mine.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Fortifcations/Claymore Mine.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 21:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mech Shovel]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A giant metal rod with a spade head on one end. It’s perfect for digging holes in dirt, sand and other loose objects. Most soldiers can dig a hole half the size of their mech in 5 minutes. This Hole grants you medium cover. You can dig a hole that gives you light cover in 4 actions. <br>It can also be used as a melee weapon when needed.<br>
Stat: Str<br>
Range: 5m<br>
Damage: 1<br>
Armor pen: Light<br>
Recoil: 4<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Traits: Melee]]></description><link>Equipment/Fortifcations/Mech Shovel.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Fortifcations/Mech Shovel.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:33:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mine Maker]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This tool helps you convert grenades into mines. You can expend a grenade to convert it into a mine of the same kind. You pick one of the following trigger conditions: When a creature move into the mine's space, when a creature moves within 5m of the mine or when a creature moves within 10m of the mine. You can also choose if the mine is instant or has the grenade's fuse timer. It takes one action to convert and deploy the mine.]]></description><link>Equipment/Fortifcations/Mine Maker.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Fortifcations/Mine Maker.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 15:48:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pop-up Barricade]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This folding metal plate rapidly unfolds when you throw it down. Granting you 180° medium cover. If you a prone behind it you gain heavy cover. The barricade has 3 hit points and the following stats. Agl 10 Com 8 Sen 7 Str 13 AR 12. It is medium armor. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Fortifcations/Pop-up Barricade.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Fortifcations/Pop-up Barricade.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:26:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sonic Mine]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This come shaped device can be deployed on the ground with laser tripwires. When a creature moves within 10m of it begins to wail a high pitched noise, that can be heard up to 500m away. Any creature within 15m of the mine while the noise is actually is deafened and must make a DC 10 Sen check or take 1 damage. You can carry 3 of these per equipment slot.]]></description><link>Equipment/Fortifcations/Sonic Mine.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Fortifcations/Sonic Mine.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 01:02:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sound Suppressor]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This spherical device clicks and whirls to life once you deploy it. Using so very advanced math and on state of the art technology it sends out sound waves to perfectly cancel out other sound waves creating a zone of total silence. When you deploy it as an action and expend a charge a 60m radius sphere of total silence is created for 20 time tokens. All creatures inside this sphere are <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FDeafened" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FDeafened" target="_blank">deafened</a>. After the time runs out you can spend an action to pick it back up or another charge to reactivate it. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Fortifcations/Sound Suppressor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Fortifcations/Sound Suppressor.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 18:44:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spotter Turret]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This Turret can be deployed as an action and it throws its own token into the bag when it’s deployed. It applies marked +1 on the nearest enemy in range. It has 1 hit point and a 9 for all defense checks. The turret shuts down after 40 time tokens.]]></description><link>Equipment/Fortifcations/Spotter Turret.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Fortifcations/Spotter Turret.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:17:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thumpers]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This device pounds the ground to create the sound waves needed to attract enemy attention. When you use a action to deploy this it begins to thump against the ground attracting the attention of any breaches or creatures in the area. Intelligent creatures will understand what this is. It has 1 hit point when deployed and you can carry 3 of these per equipment slot. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Fortifcations/Thumpers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Fortifcations/Thumpers.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 20:25:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fire Foam]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These grenades explode in bursts of fireproof foam that extinguish flames in that area. It also prevents fire from spread along the foam.<br>
Grenades per set: 4<br>
Fuse time: 1<br>
Area: 25 tiles (10m)<br>
Throw Range: Str Score x 10m<br>
Effect: The area is coated in fire foam which extinguishes flames and removes the burning condition from all creatures and spaces within that area and prevents them from regaining it for 20 time tokens.]]></description><link>Equipment/Grenades/Fire Foam.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Grenades/Fire Foam.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 18:57:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flash bang]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These grenades blind and stagger creatures caught in their blast. Be careful near friendlys.<br>
Grenades per set: 3<br>
Fuse time: 2 Player turns<br>
Area: 10m radius<br>
Throw Range: Str Score x 10m<br>
Effect: All creatures in range are staggered and blinded until the end of their next turn.]]></description><link>Equipment/Grenades/Flash bang.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Grenades/Flash bang.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:23:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Frag]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These grenades are designed to wound creatures and spread shrapnel over a large area.<br>
Grenades per set: 3<br>
Fuse time: 3 Player turns<br>
Area: 10m radius<br>
Throw Range: Str Score x 10m<br>
Effect: All creature take 2 damage or 1 on a successful Agl check. You set the DC with an Agl check. If they exceed by 3 they take no damage.]]></description><link>Equipment/Grenades/Frag.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Grenades/Frag.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:13:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goo]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These ]]></description><link>Equipment/Grenades/Goo.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Grenades/Goo.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 04:57:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[High Explosive]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These grenades are designed to wound creatures through heavy armor or damage structures.<br>
Grenades per set: 3<br>
Fuse time: 4 Player turns<br>
Area: 9 tiles (5m)<br>
Throw Range: Str Score x 10m<br>
Effect: All creature take 3 damage or 2 on a successful Agl check. You set the DC with an Agl check. If they exceed by 3 they take no damage.]]></description><link>Equipment/Grenades/High Explosive.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Grenades/High Explosive.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:12:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Impact]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These grenades explode on impact which removes the delay between throwing the grenades and them exploding.<br>
Grenades per set: 3<br>
Fuse time: None<br>
Area: 9 tiles (5m)<br>
Throw Range: Str Score x 10m<br>
Effect: The target location takes 2 damage and every other space in the area takes 1 damage unless they succeed an Agl check. You set the DC with an Agl check.]]></description><link>Equipment/Grenades/Impact.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Grenades/Impact.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:39:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Paint Grenade]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These grenades explode in colorful paint that prevents cloaking and makes it easier to mark. This bright colorful paint reflects tons of light and helps targeting systems.<br>
Grenades per set: 4<br>
Fuse time: 2<br>
Area: 25 tiles (10m)<br>
Throw Range: Str Score x 10m<br>
Effect: Each creature in range is covered in colorful paint (Thrower’s choice of color) until they can spend 3 actions cleaning it off. While painted these creatures gain a level of marked.]]></description><link>Equipment/Grenades/Paint Grenade.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Grenades/Paint Grenade.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 01:14:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smoke]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This grenade is perfect for obscuring areas from enemy sight.<br>
Grenades per set: 4<br>
Fuse time: 4 Player turns<br>
Area: 9 tiles (5m)<br>
Throw Range: Str Score x 10m<br>
Effect: The area is filled with smoke for 30 player turns.]]></description><link>Equipment/Grenades/Smoke.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Grenades/Smoke.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 05:15:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ammo bandolier]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This sling holds several pouches for ammo and magazines. You can carry 3 non belt or shell ammunition. You can destroy 2 spare ammo as 1 damage. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Misc/Ammo bandolier.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Misc/Ammo bandolier.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 03:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Automatic Tool kit]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This special tool kit can be any tool kit when you pick this equipment. It always remains that tool until you get a new one. Automatic (Tool name) is how you’ll write this into your sheet. This tool kit can be used during a break in addition to another action you take at the cost of a charge. It rolls 1d8 instead of 2d8 to determine the bonus. It gets no benefit from other equipment or upgrades that boost your roll on the break table. It has 2 hit points when it takes 1 damage it has a -2 to rolls on the break table. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Misc/Automatic Tool kit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Misc/Automatic Tool kit.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:56:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EMF Jammer]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This brick like device has several prongs sticking out of it. When you use an action and a charge all signals are jammed in a 60m radius sphere. We you activate this roll a COM check. All creatures within range when you activate it must succeed on a COM defense check or suffer EMP 1.]]></description><link>Equipment/Misc/EMF Jammer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Misc/EMF Jammer.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 20:20:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Feet spikes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Despite being based off the human ice spikes used for climbing and traction, these spikes have a greater range of utility than simply gripping on the ice. They reduce any recoil by 1, you ignore the slipperiness of ice, and have a +1 to checks to resist being shoved and climbing.<br>
They have 1 hit point and take an action to put on or take off.]]></description><link>Equipment/Misc/Feet spikes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Misc/Feet spikes.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 19:29:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Folding Solar]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This strange looking rectangle unfolds into a large solar panel to help mechs recharge. Just be careful when you take it into combat as it's quite fragile. During a break you can unfold this and set it up attached to a mech. That mech regains 2 charges if it's sunny or 1 if it's day time and there is other weather blocking the sun. This item has 1 hit point.]]></description><link>Equipment/Misc/Folding Solar.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Misc/Folding Solar.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 19:04:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pontoon Rafts]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These inflatable rafts can be set on the water to allow you to set up equipment or fight on them. These rafts swell to 10m squares that can hold up to 3 mechs of weight. These pontoons have 2 hit points and a 8 for all defense checks. When they take 1 damage the weight they can hold drops to 2 mechs. These come in packs of 4 and you can deploy 1 as an action. You can spend 5 minutes packing up an undamaged one. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Misc/Pontoon Rafts.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Misc/Pontoon Rafts.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 01:41:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rocket Boots]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These boots are fitted with trusters so you can jump extra far and cover ground faster than you'd normally be able to. Once per round, on a player turn, you can expend a charge to make a 30m jump. This item has 1 hit point.]]></description><link>Equipment/Misc/Rocket Boots.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Misc/Rocket Boots.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 00:20:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Targeting Binoculars]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These binoculars have thermal vision that let you see out to a range of 300m. While you are looking through the binoculars you can mark a creature. This creature gains marked 1 until you target another creature with the binoculars or they break. They have 1 hit point]]></description><link>Equipment/Misc/Targeting Binoculars.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Misc/Targeting Binoculars.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 01:11:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cooks Tools]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These tools are perfect for fixing up a big meal and boosting moral for soldiers on long deployments. As your break action you can cook up some food, and give each player in your team a bonus to one roll they make before the next break equal to your result on the break table. Players can only have one bonus from cooks tools at a time. <br>They have one hit point and cannot be repaired.]]></description><link>Equipment/Tools/Cooks Tools.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Tools/Cooks Tools.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 04:57:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[First Aid Kit]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This kit full of bandages, splints, and medicine. It's prefect for tending in the field and stablising creatures conditions until they can get proper treatment. As an action you can tend to a creature that has taken damage. If you tend to a player they recover any pilot damage they've taken. The First aid kit's break action is to tend to other players and roll a first aid check, they can give a number of players equal to it's check result a reroll on a defense check they fail. <br>They have one hit point and cannot be repaired.]]></description><link>Equipment/Tools/First Aid Kit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Tools/First Aid Kit.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 04:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Harvesting Kit]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>During a break you can dig through an enemy to find useful samples and other bits and bobs that will be helpful to the war effort. Roll on the break table and you’ll get that many samples. You can pick which enemies they’re from whether they’re all from one or each on is different or something in between. Mark these samples down so they can help you upgrade equipment and upgrades later. They have 2 hit points and can be repaired.]]></description><link>Equipment/Tools/Harvesting Kit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Tools/Harvesting Kit.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 02:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Navigator’s Holodeck]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This device is fitted with maps of the area, a wayfinder compass, and some recon drones to see the area. It’s perfect at positioning you, your objective, and the terrain around it. <br>During a break you can take the plan action to set a course of action for your crew. You learn the location of your check roll -1 POIs or if there are any. These POIs could be crash sites, abandoned supplies, alien nests, or anything else the GM comes up with. (There may be hostilities at these locations) Additionally you learn about any upcoming weather effects.<br>
They have 1 hit point and cannot be repaired.]]></description><link>Equipment/Tools/Navigator’s Holodeck.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Tools/Navigator’s Holodeck.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 02:54:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Radio Kit]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This portable radio can typically pick up signals from distances of 10000s of meters. It’s great for contraction nearby aircraft for support or radioing supplies or extraction. Its break action is to radio for support. You call down a number of supply boxes equal to your roll on the table. <br>They have one hit point and cannot be repaired]]></description><link>Equipment/Tools/Radio Kit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Tools/Radio Kit.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 04:56:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Repair Tools]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These tools are designed to fix up mech, vehicles, and other metal fortifications. They’re adequate at fixing computers and other tech bits but not the best. Repair tools are required to take the repair action during your break. <br>They have one hit point and cannot be repaired.]]></description><link>Equipment/Tools/Repair Tools.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Tools/Repair Tools.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 04:57:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Concussive Initiator]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This version of the initiator is filled with concussive ammo, that has a staggering effect on enemies and with consecutive hits you can push enemies away. Its ammo takes up more space and can’t fit as much per clip. May have reduced effectiveness against larger creatures<br>
Stat: Com<br>
Recoil: 3<br>
Damage: 1<br>
Range: 160m<br>
Shots per clip: 3<br>
Spare clips: 4<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Ammo type:  Magazine<br>
Traits: Concussive, one handed, ]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Concussive Initiator.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Concussive Initiator.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:01:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EMP Launcher]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>A long tube like gun designed to hit mechanical targets and stun them. With it's heavy payload it punches through some parts.<br>
Stat: Com<br>
Range: 120m<br>
Damage: 1 (EMP 3)<br>
Shots per clip: 3<br>
Spare clips: 3<br>
Armor pen: Light<br>
Recoil: 5<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Ammo Type: Mags<br>
Traits: ]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/EMP Launcher.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/EMP Launcher.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 20:09:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gravity Hammer]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This gargantuan maul is specially designed to move as much force from you into whatever you’re hitting. When you attack with this you have a +1 to hit and damage for every 15m you’ve moved in a single direction this turn.<br>
Stat: Str<br>
Range: Melee<br>
Damage: 2<br>
Armor pen: Medium(Heavy if 4+ damage)<br>
Recoil: 6<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Traits: Momentum based]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Gravity Hammer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Gravity Hammer.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 22:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heavy Flamer]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This massive burner rests on the arm of your mech with a large fuel tank. It spews fire over massive areas and leaves burning fuel on those spaces. It uses it's ammo quickly so keep an eye on the fuel gauge so you're aware when it needs a reload. If it's damaged it wastes fuel even more. After taking one damage it only hits one hex per ammo<br>Stat: None (Pick 2 hexes per ammo you're using those hexes will have <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FBurning%20X" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FBurning X" target="_blank">burning 1</a> for 10 time tokens)<br>
Range: 30m<br>
Damage: Burning 1<br>
Shots per clip: 4<br>
Spare clips: 2<br>
Recoil: 3<br>
Hit points: 2<br>
Ammo Type: Fuel<br>
Traits: Hex targeting]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Heavy Flamer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Heavy Flamer.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:03:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Initiator]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The standard UCAF weapon, this sub machine gun is handed out to the every recruit and mech. Its computer targeting system assists the poorest of shooters, making sure everyone can hit something. It’s a light weapon for mechs, but has some recoil for human infantry. It can be set to automatic from burst fire to eat ammo even faster but you hit more.<br>
Stat: Com<br>
Range: 160m<br>
Recoil: 3<br>
Damage: 1<br>
Ammo per clip: 4<br>
Spare clips: 4<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Armor pen: Light<br>
Ammo type: magazine<br>
Traits: One handed, automatic fire mode]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Initiator.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Initiator.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:59:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lightning Thrower]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This experimental weapon shoots bolts of lightning at enemies in close ranges. It often jumps from creature to creature. When you hit a creature <br>Stat: Com<br>
Range: 50m<br>
Recoil: 3<br>
Damage: 1 + Shocked<br>
Ammo per clip: 2<br>
Spare clips: 1 charge<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Armor pen: Medium<br>
Ammo type: Charges<br>
Traits: Chain 3]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Lightning Thrower.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Lightning Thrower.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:44:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Machine Gun]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This heavy rapid fire machine gun, is prefect for coving fire, suppressing enemies, and tearing through medium and lighter armor. Just set up in a position and start shooting, just make sure the enemy is dead before you need to reload. <br>Stat: Str<br>
Range: 200m<br>
Damage: 1 (x3)<br>
Shots per clip: 9<br>
Spare clips: 2<br>
Armor pen: Medium<br>
Recoil: 6(x3)<br>
Hit points: 2<br>
Ammo Type: Belt<br>
Traits: Stabilizers, Rapid fire (3)]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Machine Gun.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Machine Gun.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 08:03:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Plasma Railgun]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This massive railgun shoots burning blobs of plasma that area perfect for cutting thought enemy armor. Fortunately they don’t have a massive kick, but it keeps pushing for a while. After firing it needs some time to cooldown and recharge. It can only be fired once per round.<br>
Stat: Str<br>
Range: 300m<br>
Shots per reload: 1<br>
Spare clips: Costs 1 charge to reload.<br>
Damage: 3<br>
Armor Pen: Heavy<br>
Recoil: 4 x2<br>
Ammo type: Charge<br>
Hit points: 2 (-2 to checks with it and the r it takes 1 damage)]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Plasma Railgun.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Plasma Railgun.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pogven]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Pog-ven is a shotgun, perfect for close range combat. It’s got a high damage blast at short ranges and barely feels like a tickle at longer ranges.<br>
Stat: Agl<br>
Range: 120m<br>
Damage: 2<br>
Recoil: 5<br>
Armor pen: Medium<br>
Shots per Clip: 2<br>
Spare bullets: 12<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Ammo type: Shells<br>
Traits: Shotgun, bullet reload, double barrel]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Pogven.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Pogven.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:59:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Railgun]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This long barreled gun has a loading process similar to a double barrel shotgun. It takes a second or to charge up and fire then it fires a metal pin through almost everything. It can go through 4 objects or creatures before being stopped. Heavy armor counts as double.<br>
Stat: Com<br>
Range: 160m<br>
Recoil: 3x2<br>
Damage: 1<br>
Ammo per clip: 2<br>
Spare clips: 4<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Armor pen: Heavy<br>
Ammo type: magazine<br>
Traits: Penetration 4]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Railgun.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Railgun.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:44:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Revolver]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This six shot revolver rapid fires off pairs of shots into nearby enemies. Capable of being dual wielded to allow extra firing fun. These guns run out ammo quick so you’ll need to reload regularly.<br>
Stat: Agl<br>
Range: 120m<br>
Damage: 1<br>
Shots per clip: 3<br>
Spare clips: 2<br>
Armor pen: Light<br>
Recoil: 2<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Ammo Type: moon clips<br>
Traits: One handed, dual wield]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Revolver.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Revolver.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 03:13:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rocket Launcher]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This rocket launcher fires various rockets at enemies from airburst to anti tank, and High explosive. It's perfect for long distance engagements and is as versatile as the ammo you bring. Just be careful if preload something you’ll need an action to unload it then and another action reload.<br>
Stat: Sen<br>
Range: 500m<br>
Shots per reload: 1<br>
Spare clips: 0 Requires <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FAmmo%20pack" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FAmmo pack" target="_blank">Ammo backpack</a> or other method to carry extra ammo<br>
Damage: Ammo Dependent<br>
Armor Pen: Ammo dependent<br>
Recoil: 6<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Ammo type: Shells<br>Ammo types:<br>
Air burst: Perfect for shredding light infantry, the rocket flys until it gets close to an target then it explodes out and sends shrapnel out in a cone, to shred enemies. All creatures in a 30m cone must make a Agl save or take 2 damage. On a successful save they take 1 damage.<br>High Explosive: Perfect for big unarmored targets, the rocket flys until it hits some thing. Roll sensors to hit the first target which takes 1 damage. On a hit the rocket explodes like an <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FGrenades%2FHigh%20Explosive" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FGrenades%2FHigh Explosive" target="_blank">HE grenade</a>.<br>Anti Tank: Perfect for making through heavy armor and destroy whatever is underneath. The rocket hits and drills into the heavy armor. It has heavy armor penetration and deals 3 damage on a hit. <br>Illumination: Perfect for lighting up dark areas and revealing hidden enemies, just be careful of nearby teammates, as they might be blinded. ]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Rocket Launcher.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Rocket Launcher.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:59:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RR Cannon]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The Recoil Rocket Cannon Fires heavy 100mm shells. Clips for the RR10 are single extra large shells that cannot be carried normally. These shells fit into ammo packs or ammo bags.<br>
Stat: Str<br>
Range: 400m<br>
Recoil: 12<br>
Damage: 4<br>
Pen: Heavy<br>
Shots per reload: 1<br>
Spare clips: 0 Needs ammo pack or other way to carry extra ammo.<br>
Ammo type: Shells]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/RR Cannon.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/RR Cannon.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 18:29:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scoped Rifle]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This rifle lets you pick of individual targets over long distances. Lay prone for improved accuracy. It's so accurate you can even shoot into brawls.<br>Stat: Sen<br>
Range: 300m (Scope)<br>
Damage: 2<br>
Shots per clip: 3<br>
Spare clips: 3<br>
Armor pen: Medium<br>
Recoil: 5<br>
Hit points: 1<br>
Ammo Type: Mags<br>
Traits: Scoped, Bipod]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Scoped Rifle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Scoped Rifle.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 19:01:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shock Whips]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>These whips are thin metal wires that are strong enough to cut into steel]]></description><link>Equipment/Weapons/Shock Whips.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Equipment/Weapons/Shock Whips.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:28:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[7Y - 1ZQ]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>An electronic warfare mech designed to disable and mislead enemies as much as possible. It's fitted with Jammers to block radios EMPs to stop enemies and loads of smoke and sound devices. Just don't operate to close to this mech as you might get affected by accident. With a EMF jammer to block signals and a EMP launcher to shoot down enemies. It also has a smoke screen to block vision and thumpers to attract attention. It's fitted with a thermal camera to see through smoke and spot devices 7Y-1ZQ's come with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FEMF%20Jammer" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FEMF Jammer" target="_blank">EMF Jammer</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FEMP%20Launcher" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FEMP Launcher" target="_blank">EMP launcher</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FHead%2FThermal%20Camera" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FHead%2FThermal Camera" target="_blank">Thermal Camera</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FThumper" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FThumper" target="_blank">Thumpers</a>, and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FSmoke%20Screen" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FSmoke Screen" target="_blank">smoke screen</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 4 Com 7 Sen 6 Str 5<br>
Recommended Tool: Radio]]></description><link>Prebuilts/7Y - 1ZQ.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/7Y - 1ZQ.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:03:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[8P-YR0]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This heavy mech is designed to suffer the fire and flames while it purges tunnels, hives, and forests from planets. It's slow but effective at clean up, expect for ash, and nothing survives it's flames for very long. It's heavy flamer guzzles fuel at an enormous rate, but with itS massive fuel tank it can spew flames all day. It's fireproof plating prevent's it from getting burned while its ultra sonic sensors let it see through smoke and fire. Finally it has foam grenades to stop areas and allies from burning. It's equipped with a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FHeavy%20Flamer" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FHeavy Flamer" target="_blank">Heavy Flamer</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FLarge%20Fuel%20Tank" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FLarge Fuel Tank" target="_blank">Large fuel tank</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FShwll%2FFireproof%20Coating" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FShwll%2FFireproof Coating" target="_blank">Fireproof plating</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FHead%2FEcho%20locator" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FHead%2FEcho locator" target="_blank">Echo locator</a>, and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FGrenades%2FFire%20Foam" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FGrenades%2FFire Foam" target="_blank">fire foam grenades</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 5 Com 5 Sen 6 Str 6<br>
Recommended Tool: Cooks]]></description><link>Prebuilts/8P-YR0.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/8P-YR0.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:30:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[B8-R0S]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The B8-R0S is a heavy weapons platform that functions like an anti armor gun. It sets up in a firing position and kills everything nearby. It’s normally focused on heavy armor targets while it draws fire for weaker allies. It’s RR Cannon penetrates the heaviest of armors and obliterates whatever is on the other side of that armor. It has recoil spikes to handle the recoil that plant it into a single position with a heavy ammo pack to carry its extra shells. With a heavy armor plate and limb reinforcing it’s much harder to take down than a normal mech. The B8-R0S has the following equipment: <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FRR%20Cannon" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FRR Cannon" target="_blank">RR Cannon</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FHeavy%20Ammo%20Pack" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FHeavy Ammo Pack" target="_blank">Heavy Ammo pack</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FRecoil%20Spikes" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FRecoil Spikes" target="_blank">Recoil Spikes</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FDefense%2FHeavy%20Armor%20Plate" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FDefense%2FHeavy Armor Plate" target="_blank">Heavy armor plate</a>, and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FReinforced%20Limbs" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FReinforced Limbs" target="_blank">reinforced limbs</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 4 Com 5 Sen 6 Str 7<br>
Recommended tool: Radio kit]]></description><link>Prebuilts/B8-R0S.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/B8-R0S.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 01:24:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[C1-IM8]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The C1-IM8 is designed for deployment in canyon filled planets and it has excellent vertical mobility with its grappling system. Don’t be too scared of slips and falls with its gel padding. Its jump pack and rocket boots help it get the height it needs to cross longer divides. It has a a gravity hammer that hits harder with extra momentum. C1-IM8’s are equipped with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FCore%2FGrappling%20System" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FCore%2FGrappling System" target="_blank">Grappling system</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FGel%20padding" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FGel padding" target="_blank">Gel padding</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FJump%20pack" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FJump pack" target="_blank">Jump pack</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FRocket%20Boots" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FRocket Boots" target="_blank">Rocket boots</a>, and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FGravity%20Hammer" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FGravity Hammer" target="_blank">Gravity Hammer</a>.<br>
Stats:<br>
Agl 7 Com 4 Sen 4 Str 7<br>
Recommended tool: Navigator's Holodeck]]></description><link>Prebuilts/C1-IM8.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/C1-IM8.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 01:24:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[G3 - 0FW]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The G3-0FW is a frontline mech that is supposed to keep bullets down range suppressing enemies and tearing through hordes. Equipped with a machine gun and belt pack for constant fire power. It's arms are reinforced to handle the recoil, while it has Gyroscopic stabilizers to let it stand up and drop quickly. It's equipped with a trusty shovel help it dig into a position and get some cover for a firing position.<br>
G3-0FW's have <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FMachine%20Gun" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FMachine Gun" target="_blank">Machine gun</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FAmmo%20Belt%20Pack" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FAmmo Belt Pack" target="_blank">Ammo belt pack</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FGyroscopic%20Stabilizers" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FGyroscopic Stabilizers" target="_blank">Gyroscopic Stabilizers</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FArm%2FWrist%20Bracing" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FArm%2FWrist Bracing" target="_blank">Wrist Bracing</a>, and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FMech%20Shovel" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FMech Shovel" target="_blank">Mech Shovel</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 6 Com 4 Sen 5 Str 7<br>
Recommend Tool: First Aid]]></description><link>Prebuilts/G3 - 0FW.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/G3 - 0FW.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[M3-D1C]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The M3-D1C is designed to retrieve and repair damaged and destroyed mechs. It’s also capable of treating human wounds. With a carry pack to carry some extra supplies and a person for field repairs or a rescue mission. It has an autopilot function that lets it follow behind another mech if needed and preform basic tasks. With fine motor upgrades it’s better with a scalpel than most. It has a heavy armor plate to protect it from incoming fire. It also has. It has a tool kit that can be set up and it will operate on anyone. The M3-D1C comes with a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FCarry%20Pack" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FCarry Pack" target="_blank">Carry Pack</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FCore%2FBasic%20Autopilot" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FCore%2FBasic Autopilot" target="_blank">Basic Autopilot</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FFine%20Motor%20Controller" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FFine Motor Controller" target="_blank">Fine motor controller</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FDefense%2FHeavy%20Armor%20Plate" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FDefense%2FHeavy Armor Plate" target="_blank">Heavy armor plate</a>, and an <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FAutomatic%20Tool%20kit" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FAutomatic Tool kit" target="_blank">automatic tool kit</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 5 Com 6 Sen 5 Str 6<br>
Recommend tool first aid or repair. (Gets two,  one is automatic tool kit)]]></description><link>Prebuilts/M3-D1C.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/M3-D1C.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 01:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[R4-D4R]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The R4-D4R is a command mech favored in areas with poor visibility for its ability to find, track, and reveal enemy locations. It's also good at finding what's behind doors, walls and other barricades. It spots enemies with its SONAR and TERMOR sensors then points them out with a laser marker for allies and it can lay sonic mines to serve as a forewarning if enemies follow. Finally in a fire fight, it can throw out paint grenades to make enemies even easier to spot. The basic R4-D4R is equipped with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FHead%2FLocking%20Sensors" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FHead%2FLocking Sensors" target="_blank">Locking Sensors</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FTargeting%20Binoculars" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FTargeting Binoculars" target="_blank">Targeting Binoculars</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FGrenades%2FPaint%20Grenade" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FGrenades%2FPaint Grenade" target="_blank">paint grenades</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FTremor%20sensors" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FTremor sensors" target="_blank">Tremor sensors</a>, and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FSonic%20Mine" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FSonic Mine" target="_blank">sonic mines</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 5 Com 5 Sen 7 Str 5<br>
Recommended Tool: Radio]]></description><link>Prebuilts/R4-D4R.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/R4-D4R.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:02:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[R6-3OH]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The R6-3OH is a support mech to assist others in spotting, repairs and entrenching. With a helpful drone to spot targets and assist with repairs. Also equipped with a shovel and targeting binoculars. It has an extra arm to assist with reloading and a fine motor controller. R6-3OH is equipped with a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FDrone%20Pack" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FDrone Pack" target="_blank">drone pack</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FMech%20Shovel" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FMech Shovel" target="_blank">Mech Shovel</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FTargeting%20Binoculars" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FTargeting Binoculars" target="_blank">targeting binoculars</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FArm%2FReloading%20Arm" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FArm%2FReloading Arm" target="_blank">reloading arm</a>, and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FFine%20Motor%20Controller" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FFine Motor Controller" target="_blank">fine motor controller</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 6 Com 6 Sen 6 Str 4<br>
Recommended Tool: Repair]]></description><link>Prebuilts/R6-3OH.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/R6-3OH.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 18:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[RP-56U]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This heavy mech focuses on long range engagements taking whatever is needed to help. With its Rocket Launcher and Heavy Ammo pack it can bring a versatile set of ammo to handle whatever they need. Its pop-up barricade lets it set up where even it’s needed. While it’s enhanced zoom eyes let it focus on targets farther away. Finally its smoke screen lets it relocate after the enemy spots it. The RP-56U is equipped with a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FRocket%20Launcher" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FRocket Launcher" target="_blank">Rocket Launcher</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FHeavy%20Ammo%20Pack" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FHeavy Ammo Pack" target="_blank">Heavy Ammo pack</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FPop-up%20Barricade" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FPop-up Barricade" target="_blank">pop-up barricade</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FHead%2FZoom%20sensors" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FHead%2FZoom sensors" target="_blank">zoom eyes</a>, and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FSmoke%20Screen" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FSmoke Screen" target="_blank">smoke screen</a>.<br>
Stats:<br>
Agl 5 Com 5 Sen 7 Str 5<br>
Recommended tool: Radio Kit]]></description><link>Prebuilts/RP-56U.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/RP-56U.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:44:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SC -06T]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The SC-06T is a scout mech designed for days in the field. Whether it's laying an ambush or sneaking behind enemy lines the SC-06T is equipped for it. A cloaking skin to help camouflage  it and a sound suppressor to hide any noise it might make. It's extra servos allow it to move far faster than other mechs of its size. It's equipped with a scoped rifle so it can pick things off from a distance. Finally, its folding solar panel can be set up during breaks to recharge it even faster. The SC-06T has a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FSound%20Suppressor" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FFortifcations%2FSound Suppressor" target="_blank">Sound Suppressor</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FExtra%20Servos" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FExtra Servos" target="_blank">extra servos</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FShell%2FCloak%20skin" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FShell%2FCloak skin" target="_blank">cloak skin</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FScoped%20Rifle" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FScoped Rifle" target="_blank">scoped rifle</a> and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FFolding%20Solar" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FFolding Solar" target="_blank">folding solar</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 6 Com 6 Sen 6 Str 4<br>
Recommend Tool: Navigator’s]]></description><link>Prebuilts/SC -06T.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/SC -06T.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:29:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[T7-E1C]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This mech is designed to handle the electrical storms and radiation that befalls many planets. It can resist massive EMPs and shoot back massive bolts of lightning as whatever it needs to. It's heavy lead plating protects it from most EMPs while it's Lightning Thrower destroys everything in its path. It's fitted with a spare capacitor slot to hold extra charge. It has been given repair vials to fix various immediately on its dangerous worlds. Finally its jump pack helps it cover extra ground when other vehicles are down. Basic T7-E1Cs are fitted with <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FShell%2FLead%20Plating" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FShell%2FLead Plating" target="_blank">Lead plating</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FLightning%20Thrower" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FLightning Thrower" target="_blank">Lightning thrower</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FDefense%2FRepair%20Vials" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FDefense%2FRepair Vials" target="_blank">repair vials</a>, a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FJump%20pack" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FBackpacks%2FJump pack" target="_blank">jump pack</a>, and a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FExtra%20Capacitor%20Slot" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FGeneric%2FExtra Capacitor Slot" target="_blank">spare capacitor slot</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 6 Com 5 Sen 5 Str 6<br>
Recommended Tool: Repair tools]]></description><link>Prebuilts/T7-E1C.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/T7-E1C.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:29:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[UL-92D]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The UL-92D is designed to work in swampy conditions from marshes to overgrown forests. The UL-92D has a sealed shell to stop that swamp smell and moisture From seeping into it. I had higher torque motors to help it match through swampy terrain. Its railgun pierces almost everything when you can’t get a clean shot. While it’s pontoon rafts let it set up firing positions or other devices on the water. Finally with a belt of flash grenades to distract anything that spots them. The UL-92D comes with a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FShell%2FPressure%20sealing" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FShell%2FPressure sealing" target="_blank">sealed shell</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FHigh%20Torque%20Motors" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FLegs%2FHigh Torque Motors" target="_blank">high torque motors</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FRailgun" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FRailgun" target="_blank">railgun</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FPontoon%20Rafts" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FPontoon Rafts" target="_blank">pontoon rafts</a>, and a belt of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FGrenades%2FFlash%20bang" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FGrenades%2FFlash bang" target="_blank">flash bangs</a>.<br>
Stats: Agl 6 Com 5 Sen 5 Str 6<br>
Recommended tool: Navigators]]></description><link>Prebuilts/UL-92D.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/UL-92D.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 01:33:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Y0-KA1]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This agile mech wields a deadly pair of revolvers and it reloads them as rapidly as it shoots. Modeled after old western sheriffs it’s quick on the draw, with some exceptional predictive algorithms. With lasso to stop things from fleeing when they need to capture something. Finally to keep those guns firing it had an ammo bandolier. Y0-KA1’s are kitted with 2 <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FRevolver" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FWeapons%2FRevolver" target="_blank">Revolvers</a> (1 Replaces the Initiator), an <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FAmmo%20bandolier" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Equipment%2FMisc%2FAmmo bandolier" target="_blank">ammo bandolier</a>, a <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FArm%2FReloading%20Arm" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FArm%2FReloading Arm" target="_blank">reloading arm</a>, <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FCore%2FPredictive%20algorithm" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Upgrades%2FCore%2FPredictive algorithm" target="_blank">predictive algorithms</a>, and lasso.<br>
Stats: Agl 7 Com 6 sen 5 Str 4<br>
Recommend tool: radio kit]]></description><link>Prebuilts/Y0-KA1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Prebuilts/Y0-KA1.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 04:29:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Assist]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You help another mech reload a weapon they have a backpack for or you grant them a +2 to the next check they make. You must be adjacent to your fellow mech in order to take this action.]]></description><link>Rules/Actions/Assist.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Actions/Assist.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 23:53:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deploy]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Anytime you set up a mine, barricade or other fortification, you’ll be taking this action. Most items will say “as an action you can deploy this item” if you can deploy them. ]]></description><link>Rules/Actions/Deploy.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Actions/Deploy.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 16:33:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dive]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You dive up to half your movement speed and land prone, if you dive you take half fall damage and it doesn’t have to be assigned to your legs.]]></description><link>Rules/Actions/Dive.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Actions/Dive.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 06:57:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Escape]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>When something has you caught (a creature, a trap, or a rock formation), you can attempt to escape. You make a Def check with a stat based on what is trapping you. On a success you move 5m and are no longer under the effect that was holding you in place. ]]></description><link>Rules/Actions/Escape.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Actions/Escape.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:34:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Move]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You move up to your speed.  Some things will prevent you from taking this action such as being stuck or restrained. ]]></description><link>Rules/Actions/Move.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Actions/Move.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 16:34:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quick Move]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>(This does not cost an action)<br>
You hightail it out of where you are and get to another position. You move up to half your speed, and suffer a -2 to all checks you make until the start of your next turn. You can only do this once per round. ]]></description><link>Rules/Actions/Quick Move.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Actions/Quick Move.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 15:02:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stand up]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You stand back up after being prone. You can’t stand up if there’s a low celling or something is holding you down.]]></description><link>Rules/Actions/Stand up.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Actions/Stand up.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 15:03:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blinded]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You either can’t see anything or are trying to see something that you lack the special sensors for. You have a -3 to attack checks for things you can’t see.]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/Blinded.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/Blinded.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 07:21:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Burning X]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Whether it’s fire, sunlight, or acid something is burning a creature. A creature who is burning takes damage every X time token. A creature that is burning can spend an action to extinguish themselves, if the space they’re on isn’t burning, or if they are submerged in water or sprayed with it.(Burning 1 means every time token, burning 2 is every other)]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/Burning X.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/Burning X.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:02:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloaked]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You are invisible to normal senses, and gain the benefit of an unseen attacker if you attack someone. However some special senses can detect depending on how you became cloaked.<br>
Unless someone has special means to detect you have a +3 to attack and defense rolls.]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/Cloaked.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/Cloaked.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 15:02:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deafened]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You can’t hear and your radios are disabled  making it near impossible for your allies to communicate with you. Your allies cannot tell you where hidden creatures or traps are, you must make decisions about your actions without advice from other players.]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/Deafened.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/Deafened.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 01:46:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EMP X]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Machines hit with electro magnetic pulses suffer debilitating effects such as losing sensors and being unable to move. Players must choose X number of undestroyed upgrades, parts (Non pilot) and equipment to be disabled until the EMP condition wears off. These upgrades function as if they have been destroyed for the duration but can still take damage. If the a new EMP Condition is gained use the higher one. If a higher EMP is given pick new upgrades, parts and equipment until X are disabled.]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/EMP X.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/EMP X.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:24:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Marked X]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>All attack rolls against the creature have +1 per level of marked and if the creature is cloaked it can now be targeted.]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/Marked X.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/Marked X.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 23:19:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prone]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You either lie down or something knocked you over. You can only move by crawling which drops your speed to a max of 10m. Some weapons gain bonuses while prone, but all weapons receive a -1 to recoil. Melee attacks against you have +2 and ranged attacks have -1. You can end this condition by taking the stand up action or having someone else assist you.]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/Prone.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/Prone.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 05:47:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shocked]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>“With significant electricity anything will be shocked” -Lt Argentum.<br>
Shocked creatures are unable to use certain features they also cannot take any prepared actions or other reaction abilities. ]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/Shocked.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/Shocked.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 18:51:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Staggered]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You’re off balance after being hit hard or electrocuted. You have a -1 to all defense checks and have 1 less action until the end of your next turn. If you can only take 1 action you get 0 and the condition ends. If you’re staggered multiple times then penalty to your actions and defense checks increases for each time you’re staggered but it all ends at the end of your next turn.]]></description><link>Rules/Conditions/Staggered.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Conditions/Staggered.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 08:53:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Agility]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Agility (Agl) is your mech’s responsiveness, and es of use. High agility mechs can turn on a dime, take more actions than normal, and avoid explosions. <br>Agility weapons are highly responsive weapons, such as knifes or shotguns. Some old fashioned rifles are agility based as well. <br>Agility checks are going to be things that require reactivity, dexterity, or flexibility. Such as moving through cramped spaces, doing fine wiring, or hiding. <br>Agility defense checks are to dodge areas, dodge melee strikes and get behind cover. ]]></description><link>Rules/Stats/Agility.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Stats/Agility.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:53:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Computers]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Computers (Coms) is your mech's onboard computers and processing power, for other creature's is generally a metric of intelligence and memory. <br>Computer based weapons, have targeting systems, are EMPs or air support attacks.<br>Computer skills, include hacking, pulling up information, and relaying or uploading data. <br>Computer defense checks are used to resist EMPs, predict enemy attacks, and other electronic weapons. ]]></description><link>Rules/Stats/Computers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Stats/Computers.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 23:15:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sensor]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Sensors (Sen) is your mech's onboard sensors and information displays. It's your mech's ability to perceive it's own surroundings. <br>Sensor weapons are long range, work against cloaked creatures, or spot or reveal creatures.<br>Sensor checks help determine your mech's awareness of surroundings, spot hidden creatures or objects, and track or follow creatures. <br>Sensor defense checks, are for resisting attacks from hidden enemies, blinding and deafenong effects and long range attacks. ]]></description><link>Rules/Stats/Sensor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Stats/Sensor.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 23:36:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Strength]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Strength (Str) is your mech’s ability to lift heavy objects, handle recoil, and use heavy weapons. <br>Weapons that use strength are going to be, high recoil, rail-guns, or heavy melee weapons. <br>Some common strength checks are going to be lifting heavy objects, grappling creature and <br>Strength defense checks are going to be to, resist pushing attacks, avoid and to escape gabs, and resist effects you can’t dodge. ]]></description><link>Rules/Stats/Strength.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Stats/Strength.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:45:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Break Table]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Whenever you use a tool during a break roll 2d8 and use corresponding number as your result for your tool:<br>
0 or less = 0<br>
1-5 = 1<br>
6-9 = 2<br>
10-15 = 3<br>
16 or higher = 4]]></description><link>Rules/Break Table.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Break Table.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:59:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cover]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>From sandbags to rocks, Trees to creatures anything you get behind gives you cover. There are three tiers of cover light, medium and heavy.<br>
Light Cover could be a large boulder or tree that you get behind, most of your mech is still visible but the parts that aren't have a solid level of protection. You have a +1 to defense rolls while you have light cover.<br>
Medium Cover could be barricades, sandbags, or other objects that cover over half your mech. You have a +2 to defense checks while you have medium cover.<br>
Heavy Cover could be a bunker, pillbox or other object that covers more than 3/4th of your mech, if an arm or your head is the only thing sticking out it's heavy cover. ]]></description><link>Rules/Cover.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Cover.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 00:47:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Leveling up]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This game doesn’t have a strict level system but rank is a rough estimate of how much extra stuff you have. Bonuses that should be given out in place of level ups are equipment, Upgrades and Stat bonuses. As a GM either pick for your players or give them a list of acceptable choices based on what they accomplished. If players have samples they can modify their equipment and upgrades with extra uses, hit points, or higher bonuses. The samples should make sense for what they’re modifying ex. a ghost sample modifying a cloak skin or thermal vision.<br>
Stats bonuses should be given out less frequently than upgrades or equipment. ]]></description><link>Rules/Leveling up.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Leveling up.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:13:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Out of Mech]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>When you leave your mech you become very vulnerable to everything. All of your stats become 2s and you have a 0 AR and your speed becomes 10. You don’t gain any benefits from upgrades or equipment your mech has. You can spend an action to grab equipment from your mech and carry it but you can only carry 4 pieces of equipment. Only the things you carry can take damage for you. You can spend an action to climb into an adjacent mech without a pilot. ]]></description><link>Rules/Out of Mech.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Out of Mech.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Quick reference Sheet]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Meets it beats it. Ties are in the players favor.<br>Critical Success or failure: If a 2 is rolled on the dice that is a failure despite the total, feel free to make something especially nasty happen. If a 16 is rolled on the dice that is successful check no matter what the total is. Players deal double damage if they get this on a attack roll.<br>Turn counting: Everything with a turn clock is based on player turns. Be sure to track these, assign players to count different timers. <br>In Melee: If you’re in melee you can’t shoot guns that require two hands, or attack creature that you’re not in melee with. Unless equipment allows them other creatures can’t shoot into melee.<br>Quick move: once per round you can perform a quick move on your turn. You move half your speed and suffer a -2 to all checks you make until the end of your turn. You also don’t gain any cover bonus until the start of your next turn. Instead of moving you can instead dive 5m.<br>Unseen Attackers: If a creature can’t see its attacker for any reason: smoke, the attacker is cloaked, or sensors are down. The attacker gains a +3 to hit. This only applies if the attacker can still see their target. If something such as smoke blinds both, the attacker has no bonus but retains the -3 for being blinded.]]></description><link>Rules/Quick reference Sheet.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Quick reference Sheet.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 07:25:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Recoil Table]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>When you shoot a gun you experience recoil, with bigger weapons there’s typically more recoil. Mechs are typically strong enough to handle the recoil of their weapons but sometimes a weapon will be grabbed that someone’s not ready to fire. If your Strength plus any other effects that reduce recoil, is less than the recoil, you suffer the effects on the table based on the recoil.<br>
Recoil - Effect<br>
0- No effect<br>
1-2 you suffer a penalty to shooting attacks you make until the end of your next turn equal to the excess recoil<br>
3-4 You get staggered<br>
5-6 you take one damage and fall prone.<br>
7-8 You take two damage, fall prone, and are stunned.<br>
9+ you take 3 damage, fall prone, and fall unconscious until first aid is administered to you.]]></description><link>Rules/Recoil Table.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Recoil Table.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 05:20:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Starting Equipment]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>When players make their character start them as Rank 7]]></description><link>Rules/Starting Equipment.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Starting Equipment.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:07:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Supply box]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Each supply box is prepared with love and care from the UCAF support team. Each supply pack has one of the following: A clip of ammo, a small capacitor, a grenade or an armor plate.]]></description><link>Rules/Supply box.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Supply box.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:55:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Taking damage]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>When you get hit with attacks, fall great distances, or are suffering from environmental effects you’ll take damage. When you take damage you can assign it to any upgrade, part, or equipment that has hit points left. If an upgrade or equipment runs out of hit points you cannot use it and it doesn’t provide you any benefits until it is repaired. If it’s not out of hit points check what the penalties it has for taking damage. (Some equipment and upgrades don’t have penalties) For parts here are the following downsides.<br>Head: When your head drops to 1 hit point, you become <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FBlinded" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FBlinded" target="_blank">blinded</a> and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20Game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FDeafened" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech Game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FDeafened" target="_blank">deafened</a> until the end of your next turn.  When your head has no hit points you have a -2 to your SEN score.<br>
Arms: When your arms drop to 1 hit point, you cannot use any equipment until the end of your next turn. When your arms has no hit points you have a -2 to your STR score.<br>
Pilot: If your pilot is out of hit points, you cannot take actions until your pilot is given first aid.<br>
Shell: When your shell drops to 1 hit point, become <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FShocked" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FShocked" target="_blank">shocked</a> and <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FStaggered" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FStaggered" target="_blank">staggered</a> until the start if your next turn. you When it has no hit points you have a -2 to AR.<br>
Core: When your core drops to 1 hit point, you can’t use your upgrades until the end of your next turn. When your core has no hit points you have a -2 to your COM score.<br>
Legs: When your legs drop to 0 hit points you fall <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FProne" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FProne" target="_blank">prone</a>, can’t move, stand up, or dodge until the end of your next turn. When your legs drop to 0 hit points you have a -2 to your AGL score.]]></description><link>Rules/Taking damage.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Taking damage.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 01:57:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tokens]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Players have 2 tokens and can put 1 in and take 2 actions or 2 in and take 1 action twice.<br>
Enemies have tokens and actions per tokens listed in their stat sheet<br>
Boss abilities trigger on boss tokens<br>
Time tokens are how fast the game is going they are an update step, anything that counts tokens will be based on these. Put in 1 for each player and increase or decrease to alter difficultly. (More should be harder) Don't exceed 2 per player<br>
Special tokens will be NPCs or turrets that act every round. Each of their tokens will be specially marked so that they will take their action then.]]></description><link>Rules/Tokens.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Tokens.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:13:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Upgrade Slots]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>You have the following upgrade slots unlocked as a basic mech:<br>
Head 2<br>
Shell 1<br>
Arm 3<br>
Leg 3<br>
Core 2<br>
If something has a generic slot tag, you can put it in any slot]]></description><link>Rules/Upgrade Slots.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Rules/Upgrade Slots.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 01:03:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fine Motor Controller]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Slot Generic<br>
This upgrade allows your mech to preform extra fine motor skills. You have a +1 to all tool checks you make, including during breaks.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Arm/Fine Motor Controller.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Arm/Fine Motor Controller.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:42:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reloading Arm]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Your mech has an extra arm to assist with reloading. You can expend a charge to perform the assist action or a reload without using your action. The arm has 2 hit points.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Arm/Reloading Arm.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Arm/Reloading Arm.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 23:44:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Throwing arm]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Shoulder Slot<br>
Servos have been fitted into your mech’s arms and allow it to throw grenades and other items further. Add 30ft to the distance you can throw anything. This upgrade has 1 hit point. ]]></description><link>Upgrades/Arm/Throwing arm.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Arm/Throwing arm.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 13:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wrist Bracing]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This mech's wrists are braced to handle extra recoil. Reduce any recoil you suffer by 2. This upgrade has 1 hit point.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Arm/Wrist Bracing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Arm/Wrist Bracing.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 23:45:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amped Up Reactor]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Your mech's reactor is producing more power than normal when ever you take the recharge action you regain 2 additional charges. This upgrade has 2 hit points, you regain additional charges equal to the hit points of this upgrade.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Core/Amped Up Reactor.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Core/Amped Up Reactor.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:01:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Basic Autopilot]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Slot Core<br>
Requires Com 6+<br>
Your mech’s AI has been upgraded so it can control the mech when you’re incapacitated or out of the mech. It gets one token and action per round and it can take the move, dive, stand up, escape and deploy actions. This upgrade has 1 hit point. ]]></description><link>Upgrades/Core/Basic Autopilot.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Core/Basic Autopilot.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 16:10:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grappling System]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Slot Core<br>
This large contraption looks like a set of harpoon guns mounted on your back. As an action you can fire one of the harpoons and pull your self towards it. Choose a point within 60m and fire your harpoon at it. You can then pull yourself to that point. You move 30m towards it on the next time token and you arrive at it on the second time token if it is more than 30m away. This pack takes 20 time tokens to rearm after you arrive at your point. This upgrade has 2 hit points and loses 30ft of range after it loses the first hit point.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Core/Grappling System.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Core/Grappling System.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 23:44:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Predictive algorithm]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Your mech’s AI is fitted with an algorithm that predicts when combat is going to start and gets your mech to act before others realize until something is wrong. When combat starts you can immediately take an action. This upgrade has 1 hit point.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Core/Predictive algorithm.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Core/Predictive algorithm.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 04:28:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Capacitor Auto Ejector]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Generic Slot<br>
Your Capacitors automatically disconnect themselves and become exposed when they run out of power. You can use an action to swap an expended or damaged capacitor for a different one in your equipment list.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Generic/Capacitor Auto Ejector.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Generic/Capacitor Auto Ejector.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:56:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Extra Capacitor Slot]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Generic Slot<br>
Your mech can fit a third capacitor into it. This allows you to have 3 capacitors equipped by your mech.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Generic/Extra Capacitor Slot.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Generic/Extra Capacitor Slot.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:50:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gyroscopic Stabilizers]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Agl 6+<br>
Generic Slot<br>
Your mech’s legs are fitted stabilizers that help keep you upright. When you take the stand up action you can also move half your normal speed. You also have a +2 checks made to resist being knocked to the ground.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Generic/Gyroscopic Stabilizers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Generic/Gyroscopic Stabilizers.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 19:35:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reinforced Limbs]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Generic Slot<br>
Both your arms and legs have an additional hit point. They suffer no negative effects for losing their first hit point.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Generic/Reinforced Limbs.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Generic/Reinforced Limbs.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 13:49:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smoke Screen]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>This feature in your mech allows you to project a wall of smoke around your mech. You create a 80m long 20m high wall of smoke within 30m of you. (All points must be within 30m). This feature can be reloaded during a break. 1 hit point.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Generic/Smoke Screen.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Generic/Smoke Screen.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 19:56:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stim Auto-Injectors]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Generic Slot<br>
This upgrade keeps your pilot alive, by injecting them with a super strong painkiller. When your pilot drops to 0 hit points, they are automatically administered strong painkillers which lets them keep fighting. You can keep fighting for 20 player turns. You do not regain your pilot HP unless someone tends to you. If you're tended to during a break your auto injector use is refilled. It has 1 use and 1 hp.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Generic/Stim Auto-Injectors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Generic/Stim Auto-Injectors.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 13:49:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Echo locator]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Requires Sen 6+<br>
Your mech is equipped with an echolocation system that helps it navigate in low visibility conditions. Your mech emits ultrasonic frequency sound waves that bounce back and are converted to a visual display for you. It's doesn't work while you're <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FDeafened" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FDeafened" target="_blank">deafened</a> so avoid loud noises or noise suppressors since those will disable your receivers. Effective range of 60m. Hit points: 1]]></description><link>Upgrades/Head/Echo locator.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Head/Echo locator.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:14:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Locking Sensors]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Slot Head<br>
Requires Sensor 5+<br>
You have an additional +1 to hit marked targets. Useless if blinded 1 hit point]]></description><link>Upgrades/Head/Locking Sensors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Head/Locking Sensors.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:42:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thermal Camera]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Requires Sensor 5+<br>
This infrared camera is tuned to help spot creatures through smoke and fog. It also helps spot cloaked creatures since they have massive heat signatures. Effective range 120m. Hit points 1 Useless if blinded.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Head/Thermal Camera.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Head/Thermal Camera.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:42:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zoom sensors]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Slot Head<br>
Requires Sensor 6+<br>
Your mech’s eyes are fitted with an advanced zoom function that lets you focus on more distant targets with ease. You can make things appear up to 10 times closer than they are. Additionally you have a +1 to attacks with sensor weapons. (Any attack that uses the sensor stat.) 1 hit point Useless if blinded]]></description><link>Upgrades/Head/Zoom sensors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Head/Zoom sensors.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 20:42:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Extra Servos]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Requires Agl 6+<br>
Your hips are packed with extra servos that enhance the speed of your mech. Your speed increases by 10m.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Legs/Extra Servos.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Legs/Extra Servos.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:28:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gel padding]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>When ever you fall on to a hard surface you take no falling damage and bounce back into the air up to half the height you fell. This upgrade has no hit points and cannot be destroyed or EMPed. ]]></description><link>Upgrades/Legs/Gel padding.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Legs/Gel padding.md</guid><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 23:51:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Glue Secretion]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>The feet of your mech have been fitted with secretion devices that allow you to stick to walls and other surfaces. As an action you can expend a use and start secreting glue from your feet. Until this upgrade takes damage or you spend an action to end it ]]></description><link>Upgrades/Legs/Glue Secretion.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Legs/Glue Secretion.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:11:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[High Torque Motors]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Your legs have been fitted with extra high torque motors which let it power through tough terrain and things that restrict its movement. Any reduction of your speed is decreased by 5m, and you have a +1 to escape checks.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Legs/High Torque Motors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Legs/High Torque Motors.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 01:44:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kinetic Electric Chargers]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Requires Agl 7+<br>
Leg Slot<br>
Whenever you take the move action twice in one turn you regain a charge. ]]></description><link>Upgrades/Legs/Kinetic Electric Chargers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Legs/Kinetic Electric Chargers.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:28:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Recoil Spikes]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Slot Legs<br>
These long spikes can be extended down into the ground to stabilize a mech at the cost of immobilizing it. As an action you can extend the spikes and gain a +10 to str checks made to resist being moved and for your recoil score. While you have this benefit you cannot take the move action or quick move, your speed is zero, and you have a -3 to any agl checks you make. This effect ends if you move by any means or take an action to end the effect.<br>
This upgrade has 1 hit point if it takes damage the effect ends. ]]></description><link>Upgrades/Legs/Recoil Spikes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Legs/Recoil Spikes.md</guid><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 18:16:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shock Springs]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Let slot<br>
Your legs have tightly packed springs to absorb extra force when you hit the ground. You reduce all falling damage you take by 50m.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Legs/Shock Springs.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Legs/Shock Springs.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:52:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tremor sensors]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Requires Sen 6+<br>
These sensors in your feet allow you to detect anything underground or on the surface you’re on within 100ms you can also detect the exact location of insect breaches within that range.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Legs/Tremor sensors.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Legs/Tremor sensors.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 14:18:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cloak skin]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Skin Slot<br>
This skin layer cloaking device allows your mech to hide in plain sight, beware it produces a lot of heat. As an action you can expend a charge to gained the cloaked condition for 20 time tokens. The cloak skin has 1 hit point.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Shell/Cloak skin.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Shell/Cloak skin.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 18:54:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Conductive plating]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Skin Slot<br>
Your mech is plated with highly conductive metals that reduce your thermal profile and lets you use extra charges. Unless you have an other upgrade, equipment, or ability that produces heat you have no thermal profile. Additionally you are immune to the shocked condition. This upgrade also holds 1 charge. It has 1 hit point, and if it breaks you have a thermal profile.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Shell/Conductive plating.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Shell/Conductive plating.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:44:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fireproof Coating]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Skin Slot<br>
Your mech is fitted with extra fire resistance materials so it will almost never catch fire. It also helps you put out other people. As an action you can remove the burning condition from someone. You are also immune to the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FBurning%20X" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FBurning X" target="_blank">burning</a> condition.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Shell/Fireproof Coating.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Shell/Fireproof Coating.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lead Plating]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Designed to protect against EMPs, Solar Flares, and other radiation hazards. This lead plating helps protect against all forms of electrical damage radiation and EMPs. Anytime you receive an <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="obsidian://open?vault=Mech%20game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FEMP%20X" rel="noopener" class="external-link" href="obsidian://open?vault=Mech game&amp;file=Rules%2FConditions%2FEMP X" target="_blank">EMP</a> reduce it by 4. If this reduces it to 0 or less you suffer no effects. Additional you have a +4 to checks related to radiation. This reduces you mech's speed by 5m. This upgrade has 2 hit points reduce the EMP protection by 1 and the bonus to radiation related checks by 1 per damage this upgrade has. (Minimum +2 and 2 EMP protection)]]></description><link>Upgrades/Shell/Lead Plating.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Shell/Lead Plating.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:56:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liquid Armor Coating]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Skin Slot<br>
Your mechs Armor rating increases by 1 and reduces your speed by 5.<br>
Liquid Armor Coating cannot be damaged.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Shell/Liquid Armor Coating.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Shell/Liquid Armor Coating.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 13:47:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pressure sealing]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Skin slot<br>
The outside of your mech has been sealed from the outside environment. You have a +3 to rolls to resist gas and other environmental effects. Pressure Sealing has 2 hit points and the bonus provided reduces by 1 per damage it takes.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Shell/Pressure sealing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Shell/Pressure sealing.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:02:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Slick Suit]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 ]]></description><link>Upgrades/Shell/Slick Suit.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Shell/Slick Suit.md</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:37:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Explaining Special]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Special upgrades alter the game heavily for a player by adding or removing a mechanic. Use your discretion when letting players pick special upgrades and no player should have more than one for both balance and being fair to other players. These are meant to be the really cool upgrades, as tempting as it is to uses these for NPC mechs (If you have them) do not unless you have player buy in. These are special upgrades that are rare, expensive, and drastically alter mechs, the players are special unless they signed up to be normal.<br>No player may have more than one special upgrade.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Special/Explaining Special.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Special/Explaining Special.md</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 22:36:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Nuclear core]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>Slot Core Special<br>
Your mech has been built with a portable nuclear reactor inside that fills your mech with power and radiation. Every time you take a break, your mech takes the recharge action and recharges all capacitors attached to it. You can swap capacitors before and/or after this recharge. Due to the amount of energy produced in nuclear fission it’s highly unstable and if you take damage to the core it will explode.<br>
Your mech explodes in 6 player turns in a 50m radius. All creatures within range that 5 damage and your mech is destroyed.]]></description><link>Upgrades/Special/Nuclear core.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Upgrades/Special/Nuclear core.md</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 16:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>